thedreslyn.com 2014-02-23

# Privacy Policies & Customer Security | The Dreslyn

## PRIVACY POLICY

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Respecting your privacy and protecting your security is important to The Dreslyn. Our Privacy Policy describes what data we collect, how it is used, and the steps taken to safeguard your information. By making use of this website, www.TheDreslyn.com (the “Site”) you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding your account or this Policy, please contact us at help@thedreslyn.com.

**COLLECTION & USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

To deliver the highest standard of customer service, we receive and store personal and non-personal information about you and your use of our Site. 

Personal information is information that can be used to uniquely identify or contact you. You may choose not to provide personal information. But the personal information we request is required in order to provide our products and services to you:

  * Personal information is required during registration to process orders and services like newsletter subscriptions or customer service enquiries. We may store information for such purpose.
  * We collect personal information to deliver the highest standard of customer service and make the purchase process efficient, secure and easy.
  * Only the information necessary to the secure fulfillment of orders is stored, including your full name, shipping and billing addresses, phone contact and email address.
  * We may use your personal details for payment clearance, delivery, subscriptions, service enquiries, fraud protection and order processing, sharing features, account registration.
  * We use your e-mail address to send newsletters only if you have subscribed to receive messages from our Site. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may update your account settings or click the unsubscribe link in our newsletter.
  * We may collect information related to your use of our Site. Analysis in an anonymous form may be provided to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties to improve your shopping experience.
  * Like many websites on the Internet, our Site uses cookies to make your experience on our Site more personalized and convenient.
  * Non-personal information is information that does not have a direct association to you. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We work with companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf. Our partners may have limited access to your information for the purpose of providing such services. We do not authorize any company to use or disclose your personal information. We do not share or sell your personal information. However, we do reserve the right to disclose personal information if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * Satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request,
  * Applicable terms of use, including investigation of potential violations thereof,
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security or technical issues,
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of The Dreslyn, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * In connection with any reorganization, restructuring, merger or sale, or other transferring of assets we reserve the right to transfer information, including personal information, provided that the receiving party agrees to respect your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Our Site contains links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of information may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate with reputable websites, we are not responsible for the information handling practices of third party websites. They have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully before using those sites. 

SECURITY

The Dreslyn uses the most up-to-date website security to protect our clientele. We employ Secure Socket Layering (SSL) technology from Comodo that encrypts and protects your data when transmitted via the Internet. SSL security is denoted by “https:” in the url field at the top of your browser. And, we us Verified by Visa and MasterCard SecureCode to authenticate all credit card transactions on the site. However, we cannot assume liability for improper access to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to the computer or device through which you use your account. 

CHANGES TO OUR POLICY

As we update and expand our services, we may make changes to this policy. You should check back for updates to this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site after such changes to our Privacy Policy will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. The most current version of this Privacy Policy can be reviewed by visiting our Site and clicking on “Privacy Policy” located at the bottom of the pages. 

## TERMS & CONDITIONS

Thank you for visiting The Dreslyn, a California corporation and website. In these Terms of Use we refer to our website as the “Site”. These Terms of Use and other policies posted on the Site (collectively, referred to as the “Terms of Use” or “Agreement”) outline the rules governing you and your access to and use of the Site. By accessing or using our Site you agree to this Agreement. We reserve the right to change the terms outline in this Agreement and on the Site.

**ACCOUNT REGISTRATION**

To access some of our services you must register an account. By doing so you agree to provide information that is truthful, accurate, current, and complete. In using the Site, you accept sole responsibility for all activities conducted through your account. You alone are responsible for keeping your account information and password secure. Contact us immediately if you suspect your account security has been compromised or there has been unauthorized use of your account. 

**USER CONDUCT**

We aim to create a positive experience for all users, which depends in part on your conduct. By making use of our Site you agree: 

  * Not to interfere with other visitors’ use of the Site, or affiliated or linked sites.
  * Not to transmit viruses or other harmful, disruptive, or destructive files or functions.
  * Not to disrupt the security or privacy of, or cause harm to, the Site, services, materials, system resources, servers, or networks connected to or accessible through the Site or any linked sites.

Failure to comply with our user conduct guidelines may result in termination of your account or civil and criminal penalties. At our discretion, we may terminate any account and take actions against you for activities including, but not limited to:

  * Using any technology to attempt to hide the use of multiple accounts or disrupt any of our services in any way.
  * Impersonating others or providing any kind of false information.

**ELIGIBILITY & AUTHORIZATION**

For your security and ours, we require that all visitors purchasing items through the Site meet our Terms of Eligibility:

  * You must be 18 years of age or older. Minors must inform their parents or guardian of our Terms before registering to the Site and services.
  * You must possess a valid form of payment issued by a licensed bank acceptable to The Dreslyn.
  * You must provide accurate, valid and truthful personal and payment information.
  * You may not purchase goods for any commercial exploitation.

Placing orders with The Dreslyn authorizes us to process charges on your credit/debit card in the amount of the total purchase price of your order. It also authorizes us to use your information to perform the appropriate anti-fraud checks and transmit or obtain information about you from credit reference or fraud-prevention agencies, which may keep a record of that information. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for more information on how we use your data. 

**CONTENT**

All “Content” (text, audio or music, video, graphics, photographs, and images) appearing on the Site is the intellectual property of The Dreslyn protected by intellectual property and copyright laws. 

The Site is for your personal and non-commercial use only. Any non-personal and/or commercial use of the Content is prohibited unless expressly authorized by The Dreslyn. Unauthorized use of the Content may result in civil and criminal penalties.   
You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, commercially exploit, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any Content, software, products, or services contained within this Site. You may not use this Site, or any of its Content, to further any commercial purpose, including any advertising or advertising revenue generation activity on your own site. We reserve the right to restrict or terminate your right to use the Content in any manner in our sole discretion.

**PRODUCT DESCRIPTIONS**

We do our very best to ensure all Content appearing on the Site is complete and accurate. However, errors may occur. The Dreslyn does not warrant that product descriptions, prices or photographs are accurate, complete, reliable, current, or error-free. Please refer to our Return Policy if you feel a product offered on our Site is not as described. 

**PRICING**

All prices listed on our website are in US Dollars exclusive of taxes. By law we are required to collect sales tax and duties depending on the shipping address provided by the user. Except where noted otherwise, the list price represents the full retail price suggested by the manufacturer or supplier. All product prices will be honored except in cases of patent error. 

The Dreslyn will make sale price adjustments on items purchased up to seven days before the start date of a sale or promotion. The exact item size and style must be available for purchase at the time your request is made for an adjustment to be approved. Markdown items, or items originally purchased on sale, are not eligible for price adjustments. 

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

The Website may make available materials, information, products and services provided by third parties (collectively, the “Third Party Services”). The Dreslyn is not responsible for the views, content, products, services, safety or accuracy of Third Party Services. We offer no guarantees and assume no responsibility or liability of any type with respect to the Third Party Services. Using Third Party services is at your own risk. 

**DISCLAIMERS OF WARRANTIES; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

All materials and services on the Site are provided “as is”; Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, The Dreslyn makes no guarantees or representations with respect to our services, materials, products or the Site. We do not represent that the services will be error-free or that the Site or the servers that make it available are free of viruses or other harmful components. We recommend all users of the Site obtain up-to-date software, including anti-virus programs to protect them from computer viruses. 

In addition, some events and circumstances may be beyond our reasonable control, such as adverse weather. The Dreslyn will always do its best to aim at maintaining its services but will not be responsible for failing to meet any obligations in such circumstances.

EXCEPT FOR EXPRESS REPRESENTATIONS MADE BY THE DRESLYN, THE DRESLYN EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES RELATING TO THE SERVICE, THE PRODUCTS, AND THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, QUALITY, ACCURACY, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE DRESLYN’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY CLAIM ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE SERVICE, THE PRODUCTS, THE WEBSITE OR THESE TERMS OF USE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR IN TORT, SHALL NOT EXCEED THE AMOUNTS PAID TO THE DRESLYN BY YOU FOR THE PRODUCT(S) UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE. 

**INDEMNITY & LIABILITY**

You agree to protect, compensate and hold The Dreslyn, (and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, directors, agents, partners and employees) harmless against any claim, demand, fees, expenses or liabilities resulting from your violation of our Terms of Use or your violation of the rights of another person or entity, including the use of the Site by any other persons using your account caused by your action or inaction. 

We do not waive our right to enforce this agreement if you violate our Terms of Service and no action is taken against you.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION & PRIVACY**

You understand and agree that we may disclose information about you if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of The Dreslyn or others. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for more information about how we protect and use your information.

**GOVERNING LAW & JURISDICTION**

The Dreslyn (and all Policies, Terms and Agreements) is governed in all respects by the laws of the State of California. By using our Services, you accept and consent to the jurisdiction of the Federal and State courts of Los Angeles, CA for any court action deemed necessary by The Dreslyn to protect our Site from theft or fraud.

Any other controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, the services, the products, or the Site shall be settled by binding arbitration in accordance with the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association. Any such controversy or claim shall be arbitrated on an individual basis, and shall not be consolidated in any arbitration with any claim or controversy of any other party. The arbitration shall be conducted in Los Angeles County, California, and judgment on the arbitration award may be entered into any court having jurisdiction thereof. The award of the arbitrator shall be final and binding upon the parties without appeal or review except as permitted by California law. Notwithstanding the foregoing, either party may seek any interim or preliminary injunctive relief from any court of competent jurisdiction, as necessary to protect the party’s rights or property pending the completion of arbitration.

If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of this Agree, or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the intent of the parties as reflected by that provision, and the remainder of the Agreement shall continue in full force and effect.
